appdepository.com 2018-10-18

# AppDepository

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how we collect and treat personally identifiable information ("PII") when you use our website at appdepository.com ("Website") and Services and Software (as defined in our Terms of Service ("Terms")). In this Policy, "AppDepository", "we", "us" or the like refers to AppDepository, and "you", "your" and the like refers to the person that is using the Services. If you wish contact us regarding this Policy, or correct, update or delete your information, to please contact us.

Before submitting information to us or using the Services, please read this Privacy Policy. By visiting the Website, submitting information or using any of our products or services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and consent to having your data obtained, transferred to and/or processed. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website or the Services.

### Collection of Information

Personally Identifiable Information(PII) that we may collect:

  * We collect your personally identifiable information when you fill out a Contact Us form on our Website. The information that we collect includes your name, email address, and a description of the reason you are contacting us. As noted below, we use this information to contact you about working with us. To be noted, you can visit and use any of our products anonymously if you choose. However, If you decide not to provide certain response to our requests, you may be limited in receiving some or all of the benefits associated with any particular offer. When you send an e-mail to us or otherwise voluntarily contact us, we may retain your e-mail address and the contents of the e-mail you send.
  * We collect personally identifiable information (including, but not limited to email addresses and IP addresses) when you sign up to email notifications on appdepository.com. 

You may contact us in writing to inquire about the specific PII, if any, that we may have for collected from you and to make any changes to such information. If you do not wish for us to retain any of your PII, you may contact us in writing at such email address and we will destroy the PII as soon as practicable.

Pseudonymous Information that we may collect:

  * Anonymized IP addresses that cannot be connected to any Personally Identifiable Information.
  * Cookies. A technology that allows us to store and access limited information to analyze and improve your experience viewing our website. (Read our [Cookie policy](http://privacy.appdepository.com/cookies)).

### Use and Sharing of Information

Upon viewing our wesbite, accepting our offer, or downloading our product, a generated ID is used to provide a unique experience whilst accessing our Services. We may provide this information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering technical support or to customize your experience while viewing our websites. We may use [third-party advertising companies](http://d1izr45rt62h0u.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

AppDepository collects data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website, the website of entities for which we serve advertisements (our “Advertisers”), or the websites and online services where we display advertisements (“Publishers”). This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”). We collect information about where you saw the ads we serve you and what ads you clicked on.

We utilize machine specific information for 2 primary purposes: to ensure that our users are being delivered unique software and that the software we display is as relevant to a user as possible

We do not share your PII with non-affiliated third parties, except as permitted or required by law or legal process (such as a subpoena), as otherwise specified in this Policy or as otherwise authorized by you, including as provided below.

#### How Long Do We Keep the Information?

We retain the information we collect about and from you for as long as necessary to fulfill a business purpose or comply with a legal request. We may also choose to anonymize certain information you provide to us so that it can no longer be attributed to you if we would like to retain it for longer periods of time.

### Data Collection, Cookies and Web Beacons

Like most websites, AppDepository may use cookies and web log files to track your usage of the Website and the Services. A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer and allows AppDepository to recognize you when you visit the Website using the same computer and web browser and to provide you with personalized features. Cookies also help us understand how users use and interact with the Website, which allows us to continually improve our products and services. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience and to provide you with personalized features.

One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set when you log into your account. The next time you visit the Website, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so that you will not need to log in before using the Service. In order to change your e-mail address or password, however, you will need to re-enter your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Website you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Website, we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the Website. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. Tracking technologies are used to gather statistical data on users and more generally to improve our services and the offering Programs on the Website.

In addition to our cookies, when you visit the Website your computer may receive cookies from our advertisers and from other potential sites. Such cookies would be inserted by those third parties and are not covered by this Policy, but rather, by the policies of those advertisers and outside websites.

Read more about our Cookie Policy

### Children

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will not knowingly provide access to the Website or any Services to, or collect any PII from, persons under the age of thirteen (13). If you are under the age of 13, you may not use our Services. If we learn that you are under the age of thirteen (13), we will take appropriate steps to remove your information from the database and restrict you from future access to the Website or the Services.

### Users From Outside the United States

The Website is hosted in the United States and is governed by United States law. If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Website, you consent to your information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Security

We take precautions - including technical, administrative and physical measures - to safeguard your information. We use technical safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption. We authorize access to PII, including email addresses, only for those employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. We also enforce physical access controls to our facilities and files.

Although we take commercially reasonable steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your PII, searches or other communications always will remain secure. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your PII, we will notify you if reasonably possible and as reasonably necessary so that you can take appropriate protective steps. You should also take care with how you handle and disclose your PII. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's Web site at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

### Account Information and Preferences

You can terminate your account at any time by sending a request via our contact form. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

AppDepository may update this Policy at any time. The latest version of this Policy will always be available at http://privacy.appdepository.com/privacy. Please check this page occasionally to make sure you are aware of any updates.
